https://www.louwstraining.com/privacy-notice/

Louws TrainingBusiness Consulting - Executive Coaching - Sales Training
Contact
December 11, 2020You are here: Home / Privacy NoticePrivacy Notice
Louws Management is committed to protecting the privacy of those who visit our www.louwstraining.com website.
As part of our normal operations, we collect information about our website visitors; however, we have structured this website so that you can visit Louws Management on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.
This privacy policy describes the information we do collect and how that information may be used to provide you with the optimal online experience.
Collection of Personal Information in Forms
Certain pages of Louws Management’s corporate website contain forms that allow you to request information about our services and solutions or to apply to become a Louws Management partner, or to respond to a Poll or survey.
In completing one of these forms, you may be required to provide contact information, such as your name, phone number and email address. Louws Management may use the contact information from these forms to respond to your request and send you the information you need. We do not disclose any information we receive from these forms to third parties.
Usage of Cookies and Spotlight Images or Web Beacons
Louws Management uses session cookies to limit popup windows to a single browser instance. We also use Javascripting in cooperation with cookies and “spotlight images” or “web beacons” to track website traffic and email response.
A “spotlight image” or “web beacon” is an electronic image, called a 1-by-1 pixel or clear GIF, that can recognize certain types of information on a visitor’s computer, such as a visitor’s cookie number, time and date of a page view and so on. These methods do not collect any personal information, but simply aggregate information that allows us to research patterns of behavior on our site and learn how to better meet your needs.
Our online store is powered by Microsoft bCentral. Microsoft bCentral is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. They use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, they store the personal information you provide on computer servers with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities.
Additionally, when they transmit sensitive personal information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, they protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Microsoft bCentral requires you to enable cookies to utilize our online store.You may refuse cookies by turning off that feature on your web browser, but we do not recommend doing so.
Opt-Out Policy for Email Publications
If you have opted in to receive any of our email publications, you can opt out of future publications by replying to any email you receive from us with ‘Unsubscribe’ in the subject line, or by following the “unsubscribe” instructions contained at the bottom of any email that we send to you.
Security
Information received from www.louwsmanagement.com visitors is sent to a secure location on our servers, where it is then stored in a secure database. Louws Management uses the highest levels of security to protect the integrity of our customer data.
Email
Louws Management has placed a convenient email form on this site to allow you to contact us directly. The information you provide is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. Your comments may be stored to improve the quality of our site and our services.
Legal & Copyright Disclosures and Statements
Click here for Louws Management’s legal policy regarding this website and its copyright content used as part of its training, coaching and consultations.
Questions About the Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your interactions with this site, please contact:
Louws Management Corporation, Inc.
Attn: Privacy
P.O. Box 130, Vail, Arizona, 85641 : (520) 664-1881
Click here to contact Louws Management via email.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Any changes to Louws Management’s website privacy policy will be posted in this section.
Share and Enjoy:
Enter your email to receive updates and tips from Louws Training!
Top of PageCopyright © 2020 ·
Genesis Framework · WordPress · Log in
